本片字幕根*n√斓鼐品影* http://hjtd.5d6d.com/
*鬼R小精`*的版本由PrettySnail修改！
片名：糖果
g迎高手修正！更多精彩影，M在
*n√斓鼐品影* http://hjtd.5d6d.com/
我初次遇P蒂
When I first met Candy
r光如果汁般甜美
Those were like the days of juice..
一切都得S富多彩
Everything was bountiful...
B涸谔炜瞻肯
Birds filled the sky ...
一股暖流在我之g流淌
a great kindness float through us...
天堂
Heaven
o你!
Here it is.
@次我用你的k法
I'm gonna try it your way this time.
坦白f，@k法不e
This is just as good this way. Honestly.
Then why don't you do it?
那你怎N不邮
舒曼，槭颤N我不邮
Schumann, Why don't I do it?
P蒂，丹只是跟班，不是老大
Dan is a follower, Candy. Not a leader.
吸c海一直用鼻子吸
We stick to snorting, keep it simple.
有r候，你要敢於L不同！
You know...Dare to be different!
我J槲去浴盆
Well I think I'd like to try it in the bath.
@就是不同
well that's different.
P蒂
Candy?
Candy!
舒曼，快臀遥
Schumann, fucking help me!
怎N了
What??
快
Come here!
快恚？
Come here!Babe?
噢，天哪
Oh, Christ!
死，她z入^量了
Shit, I think that she took too much.
Babe!
快o我些生理}水或者e的什N|西,我需要生理}水
Fucking saline solution or something?I need saline solution!
什N？
What?
我操！so拿杯水恚
Fuck it!Go and get a glass of water...
放}M去，快！
Put salt in it! Hurry up!
醒醒，
Come on!Babe!
P蒂，看著我！
Candy! Look at me!
放多少}？
How much salt?
我不知道！看著放吧
I don't know! HEAPS!
快他啊，_保充分溶解
Just fucking stir it! Make sure it's dissolved!
快恚∴蓿！FUCK!
Come here!Oh baby？Fuck!!
哥海@有屁用！}能乾啥！
I don't think this works man!What the fuck's salt gonna do?
]嘴！
Shut up!
操！扶著她的胳膊
Fuck!Hold her arm!
你他扶著她的胳膊！
Hold her fucking arm, man!
用力！
Harder!
@不...(管用的)
This will not be ...
_始吧
Here we go ...
不，它完全不起作用，狗屎！
No, it's not gonna fucking work!It's bullshit!!
]上你的貘f嘴
Shut up!
叫救o
Call an ambulance.
我走
Here we go.
P蒂，看著我
Candy, look at me.
P蒂！P蒂！
Candy! Candy!
P蒂，看著我！
Candy, Look at me!
Babe ...
她回
Bring her back.
...回
...back.
我他已放了不少}了
Enough with the fucking salt.
感X很美妙
It was beautiful.
我有co
Intense.
未盹h忽不定
The future or the thing that gleamed.
下如此美妙
The present was so very, very good.
我]想^去P蒂的生命
I wasn't trying to wreck Candy's life
我努力使自己得更好
I was trying to make mine better.
我渴望分享所有一切
We wanted to share absolutely everything.
尤其是最好的
Especially the best bits .
我要永h和你在一起
I want to stay with you forever.
l不想呢？
...and who would'nt!
的是我z！
It's us!
我Q之
It's called "The afternoon of extravagant delight. "
『狂g的午後』
By Candy Wyatt.
太美了
It's beautiful.
我喜g@N感X
I love it!
卡斯珀
Casper.
卡斯珀，是丹啊
Casper, It's Dan.
丹尼，等等，我即е倮和祈\而
Daniel, hang on!, I'm coming in on a win and a prayer!
什N？
What?
我正著在迪拜降落
I'm trying to land a Jumbo in Dubai.
你秀逗了？
What?
卡斯珀就像你一直想要的父H
Casper was like the dad you always wanted.
他允S你吃糖果和冷
The one that lets you have lollies and fizzy drinks
他允S你晚w
he lets you stay up late,
允S你晚上一直看影
and watch movieslate at night.
丹尼，你好
Daniel, how are you?
卡斯珀和我是多年的朋友
Casper and I went way back.
我勰悖ǚㄕZ）
I love you
我f的幔
Is that right?
是的
Yes!
@是讨
This is George.
罕的英人，本X(指男性那)雄厚
A very limited English,but a very large penis.
我f的]e吧，讨
Isn't that right, George?
你f是就是吧
Ok.
我Lonely Planet 95年出版的哈瓦那旅行指南f起
Our entire conversation is based on the 1995 "Lonely Planet" guide to Havana
坐
Sit down.
都是好朋友嘛
Just good friends.
今天有什N安排
So, what's on the agenda today?
]啥，我想四逛逛
Not much, we're just wandering around.
嗯，能不能借o我50K
Um, Could you spare us $50?
P蒂，他赤裸裸的^望你y堪了
Does is ever embarrassed you, Candy?...His naked desperation!
裸w，我可以付
Nakedness, I can deal with!
或者o我一些迷幻，我可以拿去u幔
Or give us some ecstasy .we can sell for it?
只怕我作橐幻分扑商的
I'm afraid that my days as a manufacturer of ...
日子已到^了
recreational farmaceuticals has come to an end.
槭颤N呢？
Why's that?
我F在是有C化W副教授了
I've been made Associate Professor of Organic Chemistry.
-哇瑁」喜你！-太棒了！
-Wow! Congratulations. -Great.
因此，我要So我的u
So, suddenly I have a reputation to uphold.
那N既然如此，100K可以不？
Well in that case, could we make it a hundred?
我你的！
We'll pay it back!
x了，卡斯珀
Thanks, Cas.
你]事喊桑
Everything's alright, isn't it?
只是F金周D}，七天而已
It's just a cash flow problem.Only 7 days.
你呢，P蒂
And you, Candy?
@是l通向死亡的新路！
Being one that's so new to the path of the dead!
她很好
She is fine.
嗖
When you can stop,people don't want to...
必受其y
... and when you want to stop,You can't!
生命就像Y子
One of life's little riddles!
省省吧，老太太
What Grandma?
你可以走了
Off you go!
xx你，卡斯珀
Thank you, Casper.
你好了幔
Okay, are you ready?
一,二,三...
One, two, three ...
我像《芝麻街》e的角色一永Щ
I feel like some confused Sesame Street character!
_
Start the car.
我父母很久以前就ξ曳湃巫粤髁
My own parents had long since cut me adrift
P蒂的父母，相反地，管教很
The Wyatts, on the other hand,kept their firm hold on the ropes.
要土豆幔
Do you want more potatoes?
我喜g磉@海就是榱舜箫口福
It was nice to visit places where the fridge was always full.
下次磉@何乙上P子
I shall have to bring my plate round when I come here!
我想你lF那是部分碳水化合物
I think you'll find that's part of the carbohydrate.
你有主意]？
What do you think?
我不知道 我不知道
I don't know.I don't know.
看你怎N做了
See how you go.
架？
Stretchers?
就是在木架子上上帆布
They're like wooden frames you stretch the canvass on.
不管怎樱我X得很蠢
and anyway, I feel really stupid ...
我大s一月前做的，我把我的存款都搭在架上了
I did about a month ago,and as of tomorrow I'm gonna lose
our deposit on the stretchers.
恕我冒昧地一句
It is really rude to ask ...
至少我不想令她感到@
but at least I won't surprise her!
下次你我X
I can give you the money back the next time I see you again.
你能o他打，他等一星期
Can you ring him, and tell him to wait for a week?
上星期我已很努力地L^了
I already tried that pretty much last week.
我o他打怎樱
What if I rang him for you?
我]Э
I haven't got the card with me.
多少X
How much is it?
150K
150.
不是X的}
Mate, the question is not the money.
我非常感激
I really appreciate it.
}是...我女旱
The question...is the future of my daughter.
她直妙O了
Mate, she's fantastic!
你看看她的作
Should see her paintings!
}出在你身上
The question is you.
你打算何r有所作
When are you gonna do something?
我已有了主意
I've got some ideas.
我o一些衢Ts志寄去了我的作
I've sent some of my poems into Heat magazine.
-咖啡砹!-牛奶...糖，在那!
-Here we are! -Milk...and sugar, There!
-xx你，甜心 -xx你，伊R恩
-Thanks babe! -Thanks, Elaine.
你不再是小孩了
You're not a teenager anymore.
你知道@回事，不是
You know that, don't you?
是的，我知道，吉姆
Yes, I know that, Jim.
所以我不想你做@事
that is why I did'nt want you to do it!
e啊，它很好，很棒
No, it's alright! It's fine!
你瞅瞅!你把它全弄M奶油e去了!
Look at it!You've turned it into butter!
我告V^你用混的
I told you to keep it on blend!
我用的是，因槲以奶油
I put it on "Whip", because I'm whipping cream!
但是你一[不通
Yes, but you don't know how to use it.
好吧，你砼
Right... You do it!!
-!!已太t了! -啊!很抱歉!
-Uhh!Well it's too late now! -Ah well!! Excuse me!!
所有O置都是相P的，如果你不熟悉它的操作...
Well all these settings are relative,
and if you're not familiar with the workings of the machine ...
那@樯著『拌』
Then why the fuck does it say "Whip"?
我要o他做冰激凌
I'll give them ice cream.
eRR咧咧的
And please don't swear.
好吧!我本打算o你做冰激凌，F在只能o你奶油了
Right!Well, I was going to give you cream,
but I'm going to have to give you Ice Cream.
-一切都利幔 -我活在希望之中
- Everything okay in there? -Well, we live in hope!
@是好居所
A good place to live.
去吧!!
Go!!
我不知道@是否？
I wonder if that was it?
是否什N？
If that was what?
我的（指毒品）耗M了
The last shot.
我不在乎
I wouldn't care.
@是祖母留下的
It was my Nana's.
我不u任何|西，我只是⑺典出去
We're going to sell anything.We're only hocking it!
H回淼
We'll get it back!
25K
$25.
他不想要@些
and He doesn't want the paints.
我回淼
I'll be back!
他f也S我另想k法
He said maybe we could work something out!.
_
Let's go!
是的，我跟他上床了
Yes, I fucked him!
榱50K
For $50.
我真v!
I stink!
你]}吧?
You okay?
我很抱歉
I'm Sorry.
e@!
Don't be!
@是一o人知缘纳畈匾丫玫拿孛
Here is the deepest secret that nobody knows .
@w生命之洌它是根之根,是芽之芽
Here is the root of the root,and the bud of the bud...
是天空的天空
and the sky of the sky,in the tree called life .
它高^`魂之期盼，不能被思想[藏
which grows higher than soul can hope, or mind can hide .
它是繁星保持距x的奇E
and this is the one that is keeping the stars apart.
我把你的心г谏砩
I carry your heart.
用我的心⑺妥善保藏
I carry it in my heart.
你嫁o我
Will you marry me?
我成榉蚱
We will be man and wife.
共YB理
One flesh.
你是否自承婚姻的任
I will ask them if they freely undertake the obligations of marriage ...
K且_定]有法律障K
... and to state that there is no legal impediment to the marriage.
你准浜昧,完全自K且]有任何h地...
Are you ready,freely and without reservation ...
把自己IoΨ蕉成就一段美M姻
to give yourself to eachother... in marriage?
是的，我准浜昧
We are!
你是否意互相敬郏彼此忠\
Are you ready for love and honor each other ...
相敬如e，共度N生
as husband and wife, for the rest of your life?
我意!
-We are! -We are!
P蒂，丹尼
Candice and Dan ...
回恚H鄣
Come back, love.
啊，好的
Ah, okay.
大家靠近一c，珍妮，馇蛲下一c
Alright everyone, Close together! Balloons down, Jenny.
大家笑一笑!大喜的日子!
Big smiles, everyone! Happy Day!
一，二...哇靠
One, two... Oh, Shit!
舒曼!
Schumann!
-一，二...三! -好...
-One, two... Three! -Right...
大家不去吃c汉赛c海
Alright everyone! Back to our place for a few drinks,and a bite to eat?
很抱歉，我必走了，我有s
I'm sorry, I'm going to have to go,I've got an appointment!
哦，好吧，希望其他人]有s
Oh! Well, I hope that nobody else has got an appointment!
特夫人，我可是期待很久了
I'm in for the long hall, Mrs. Wyatt.
很好
Good.
不，我恨拼
No, I hate spelling!
我也是!最恨拼和W!
Yeah, me too! Spelling and maths!
我一直ζ和W深和唇^
I was always hopeless at spelling and maths.
-我喜g英文 -英文?
-I like English. -English?
就像故事之？
Like stories and stuff?
Yeah!
英文和w育!
English and Sport!
那你可不能行差踏e
Well you can't go wrong there.
你可以做w育者
You can be a Sports journalist.
真的
Really?
我一看你就是w育者的料
I could see you as a sports journalist.
好嘛，丹尼，你真可笑
Well, Dan, you're laughing mate!
瓦@π》蚱薨
Financing this love as a married couple.
你已得到了你最想要的，你樗付出了你的一切
You get the first one under your belt,
you pour everything into it.
竟，你要的K]有低於你的最低期望
After that, the minimum equity is what you're after.
你F在累累
You get into as much debt as possible.
婚姻可使你更Ｗ⒁恍
It gives you some focus.
我不HH在f不赢a
I'm not just talking about real estate.
我在跟你生活的哲W
I'm talking about a philosophy.
不好意思，打_一下
Would you mind...if you excuse me for a minute?
便!
No! Sure!!
你和丹去打算哪憾让墼?
Where are you and Dan going for the honeymoon?
-需要檬水? -xx!
- More lemonade?  -Yeah, thanks!
你太o了!明年N中W了?
You're so tight! You're selling next year?
阿波茨路!就在我附近!
Abbots Road! It's just round the corner from us!
天哪,那有所不同的，嗯?
Geez, that'll be a change, eh?
耶，我想x州立W校，但是我父母...
Yeah, I'd rather go to a state school,but, it's mom and dad...
珍妮,^臀遗三明治
Jenny, could you come and help with sanwiches
我也褪,P珀阿姨
I'll give you a hand too, Auntie Cap!
-咋了? -你在那呵嘛?
- What? - What are you doing in there?
]乾什N
Doing a shit.
你小子有鬼!
No you're not!
_T
Open the door.
不行!
I can't!
你@婪的s碎
You greedy fuckup!!
Y婚是相自私的x
Rather a selfish way to begin a marriage!
真的！全完了！
Really! All done!
蠢！
Dick!
@然，@是凫栋a君子的周末！
Obviously, it was a big dope weekend!
l不想在自己的婚Y上放松
You wanna be relaxed at your own wedding.
-Υ宋液鼙歉 -@]什N
-Sorry about that. -That's fine!
我f到哪毫耍
So where were we?
我f了，你L...
I was saying, you need to get your t...
你不坐幔空坐吧！
Do you need a seat? Yeah, sure! Have a seat!
吉姆，你了解市
You need to get your toe in the the market, Jim!
你明白我的意思幔孔〉竭h郊，很好！
You know what I'mn saying? Out of suburbs, fine!
砷gP房...
Two bedroom...
你不需要Щ@庭院幔
...You don't need a garden courtyard, do you?
你竟然在最棒的街^住最差的房子！
You want the worst house, in the best street!
你需要N房或者浴室吧...
You don't need a kitchen or bathroom...
再f吧！
Put it in later!
比方f，你要借...
Say for example, you want to borrow ...
400K
400.
或者300
Or 300
你想借X...你刃斗...
You do it...You Struggle...
你的明白？
Understand?
丹？
Dan?
丹！
Dan!
丹...
Dan...
醒醒
Wake up.
丹，丹，醒醒
Dan, Dan, wake up.
我K了
I'm fucked.
他喝了太多的香
Too much champagne.
我...我可以肯定
Yeah I'm...I'm sure it's that...
@是大日子
Well, it is the big day!
我煮c嚎Х
I'll make some coffee.
他醉了！
He's drunk!
你想和我些什N幔
Is there anything you want to talk to me about?
什N？
What?
l生什N事了？
What's going on?
，你知道的！
Mum, you know what's going on!
我要享受一段美好r光
We are having a lovely time!
我不是那意思
That's not what I meant.
那N，我就不知道你什N意思了
Well then, I don't know what you mean!
丹咋了？
What's wrong with Dan?
他醉了，，他]什N
He's just pissed, Mum!He's hopeless!!
Σ黄
Sorry.
xx你的盛情款待
Thanks for the beautiful reception.
你要知道，那馑滥愀赣H的
It'd kill your father, you know.
你不J槲戒掉
Think we should stop?
-什N？y道我不蝮w面幔-是的，很w面！
-What? Now that we're respectable? -Yeah, I know!
你知道我的意思
You know what I mean.
任何r候你f的『戒』@~，我都明白
Whenever you say the word.
我是谘e最酷的人
We are the coolest people in McDonalds!
我有很多c
We had a lot going for us.
我lF了⒁磺芯酆掀淼拿卦E
We'd found the secret glue that held all things together
在一]有噪音的
in a perfect place...
完美之地
...where the noise did not intrude.
我的世界是如此...完整
Our world was...so very complete.
大地
Earth
-嘿，！-嗨！
-Hey baby! -Hi!
它怎N樱
How was it?
都差不多
About the same.
o你200K
Here's $200.
我大概需要半R^
I'm gonna give it half an hour and then I'll split!
耶，我不太久，家e
Yeah. I won't be long.I'll meet you at home.
好的，家e
Ok, I see you there.
好的
OK.
有人f，用不了十年你就成橐幻吸毒者
They say that for every 10 years you've been a junkie ...
你花七年等待
You will have spent 7 of them...waiting.
一花同拥rg思考
One way is not bad have as much time to think .
一忍受著工作的苦
on the other, the anxiety was a full time job!
-嘿？-你@v人！
- Hey? - You slimey cunt!
-咋了？-你他怎N看@事海
- What?  - What do you fucking reckon?
我只是稍微快了c海啥也]有
I just had a quick little bit! It was nothing!
哪e？
Where?
唔，公@。我遇安吉的r候
Um, In the park. When I met Ange.
安吉拉和你一起那啥了？
Did Angela do it with you?
]，然]，我交易完就x_了
No, of course not!
We left as soon as we did the deal!
他可以w面地回家他女友.你本硪部梢裕
Only because he's decent enough to go home to his girlfriend.
Like you should be!
哦，P蒂！他u我大麻！樯端想著在公共所e涫g迎？
Oh candy! He sold me the dope! Why would he want to have a hit
in the public toilet?
那你他也@N想？
Well why the fuck would you?
哇瑁÷著，我承J@很蠢！
Oww!Look, I admit it was dumb!
你M意了？
Okay?
我很z憾！
I'm Sorry!
我o你Lc禾痤^吧！
Will you let me make you a nice taste!
白V，我@樱
I'm getting sick of this, dickhead!
你的}出在哪海
What is your problem?
你就是我的}！
You are my problem!
你的存在直是在浪M空g
You are a waste of space.
你找到了自己的人生或其他什N幔
Are you getting your period or something?
]有，丹！
No, Dan.
我再也]有自己的人生了！
I hardly have my period anymore!
因槲业纳眢w已沈S了！
...because my body's all fucked up!
是你把我нM@死的綮v
It's this fucking nightmare you've led me into!
哦，是幔课矣心指著你的^你吸毒幔
Oh right! Like I held a gun to your head! Did I? Eh??
我有逼你@N做幔
Held you down, hit you up, did I?
操你大！
Fuck You!
操你的，P蒂！
Fuck you too, Candy!
那好，我操你全家！
Well, Fuck you double then!
丹，你lF]有，我越J真，得越差
Dan, have you noticed, the more I work, the less I paint?
P蒂，我不想吵！
Candy, I don't want a fight! OK?
我就是不明白今晚你是怎N了！我是f...
I just don't see what your problem is tonight! I mean...
我一起生活！
We've got a life!
@]有什N好闹分！
It's neither good nor bad! OK?
你知道...你知道我在做什N幔
Do you know... Do you know what I do?
仔著，蠢！
Listen to this, dick fuck!
我整天都在乾嘛？
What do I do all day?
我恨我F在的境r！
I fuck men I hate!
-e@  -我怎Nk？
-Don't do this. -What are going to do about it?
看@，就靠@！不是幔
Look, Okay, that's it! Alright?
]有妓院，]有陪伴！
No more brothels, No more escorts!
-我正_始湫碌纳活！ -你根本不懂
-We're gonna take the time to start a new life!
-You don't understand do you?
@就是我的新生活，^去的它^去吧
That's really it this time.That's going away!
或S我想^m
Maybe I want to keep using!
你知道，我工作，是的，但是
You know, I'm sick of working,yes,but...
假如我要^m吸毒，你怎Nk？
...What if I want to keep using?
What are you gonna do about it?
P蒂！
Candy!
你怎N不去找同性
Why don't you ring gay blokes?
你_始工作！你去u自己的屁股！
You start working!You hock your ass!
嘿，你不可以@N做
Hey, you know you can not do that!
你想想，我...我得艾滋！
You know, I'll get...I'll get AIDS!
你不，白V！
No you won't, you moron!
你可以跟所有人一佑帽茉刑
You'll make them use condoms,like everybody else!
我不知道怎Nk
I wouldn't know what to do.
你是性伲Π桑磕阒灰做你擅L的事情就行了
You're heterosexual, right? So you're
just doing what you're good at anyway.
你知道自己在f什N幔
Did you even hear what you're saying?
我去乾女人，]}！
Let me fuck women, no problems!
如果我乾女人可以礤X，我保C你不用工作
If I can do it with women, I'd make us all the money!
You'd never have to work, I swear!
但是...@些女人不是喜g肌肉男幔
But... These women, they want muscle types, don't they?
如果做有市觯我芬庾觯但是我不J橛惺
If there was a market out there, I'd do it, but I don't think there is!
而且你要知道，我不可能成橥性
And I'd be hopeless with the gay stuff!You know that!
你他的真令人y以置信
You're fucking unbeleivable!
_著我睡不著
I can't get to sleep with that on.
你能P了它幔
Can you turn it off?
P蒂，@的_是部秀的影片
Candy, it's a really good movie!
我把音{小一c，可以幔
I'll turn it down, okay?
不管怎樱半小r就Y束了
Anyway, it finishes in half an hour.
去你的！
Fuck you!
上床！
Go to bed.
到]有？
How can you even hear that?
光乾_到我了！
The light's bugging me!
我o法相信
I can't believe it.
我真他y以相信
I can't fucking believe it.
有怎N了？我]l出任何屿o
What? I'm not making any noise.
是光！
The light!
有光我睡不著！
The Light's keeping me awake.
好吧，我把光遮起恚行了幔
OK, look! I'll cover the light!Hmm??
@庸饩就]那N了！
There's more light coming from the workshop than that!
混蛋！
Asshole!
P！我P^的音！
The pen!! I can hear the pen scratching on the paper!
@太荒了，P蒂！
How? This is ridiculous, Candy.
你在找借口！
You're just looking for an excuse!
P羯洗玻
Turn off the light and come to bed.
我不想再和你@件事
I'm not going to discuss this with you anymore!
P簦
Turn the light off!
不！我也不想跟你f！
Nope! I'm not even talking to you!
-P上@死的 -啊哈！
-TURN THE FUCKING LIGHT OFF!! -...Aghhh!
我操！
FUCK!!
哦，我天！哦，我的天哪！
Oh my God! Oh my God!
-靠！  -Σ黄穑丹尼！
-Shit. -I'm so sorry, Danny!
-什N|西？-哦，我的天！哦，！哦，糟糕！
-What the fuck was that? -Oh my God! Oh baby! Oh shit!
天哪，流血了！
Jesus! It's fuckin' blood!
我不是故意到你的...
I didn't mean to hurt you...
西瓜，香蕉，你的大巴拉!
Jesus fuckin' shit, alright!.Fuck!
可以用岱幔
Is there any chance for some morphine?
我很疼
I'm in a fair bit of pain.
我不X得你需要岱
I don't think you need any morphine.
我X得你不太疼
I don't think you're in much pain at all!
值得一啊！
Oh well, it was worth a try!
打_了，你不介意我拿善颗Ｄ贪桑
Excuse me, would you mind if we um,
bought a couple of flavoured milks off you?
-拿去吧 -你_定？
-Just take a couple. -You sure?
e心！
No worries!
-要c@？-是的
-Want some of this? -Yeah!
-祝你^愉快的夜晚！-xx -xx你
-Have a good night! -Thanks. -Thankyou!
要幔
D'you want anymore?
有一]那了
It's been a while.
是啊，有一了
Yeah! It's been a while.
到你的^，我真的很染
I'm sorry I hurt your head.
我你好好起淼
I'll get you back!
喂，有人在家幔
Hello.... Anybody home?
你他是l？
Who the fuck are you?
是我，菲
Yeah, it's me! Phil.
菲利普_德利，商I不赢a
Phillip Dudley,from Commercial Realty.
我之前o你寄^信
I've written to you lately.
-有什N}幔-@...
-What's the problem? -Well...
我是想通知你，嗯...
We've been writing to you about...Um...
我把信..呃..放在..呃..@
I've got these..er.. hang on..Er, here they are!
三封信件的陀〖，我最近寄o你的...
Copies of the three letters we've sent you recently...
P於...呃...你欠下的租金
Relating to the matter of your er,rent in arrears.
我^泶_J一下，第三封信是通知你搬出
I'm here to confirm that the 3rd of these
letters is in actual fact a notice to vacate.
在七天之
Effective 7 days hence.
我日！
Fuck!
事上你收到信已28天了
Well of course it was...28 days when you received the letter.
F在，我今天泶说某踔...
Now, what I'm actually here for today...
是要指明你的透支情r
is to point out to you the shortfall owing on the fault of your bond.
假如..你直到下周三不能交租
Assuming... you've paid no more rent between now and next wednesday...
我算^，r你⑼钢..呃..1125元
We've calculated that the shortfall will be er... $1,125.
著，菲利普...
Listen, Phillip...
...我z都吸毒！
...we're junkies!
我是娼妓！
I am a hooker!
他游手好e!
He's hopeless!
@右恚事情好像得碗s了，我一分X也]有
Right now, things are very complicated! We haven't got any money.
是的
Right.
但是@很好
But it was good...
日子得Dy
Right when times got tough...
有卡斯珀臀
There was always Casper. .
啊，年p人
Ah, the young ones!
嗨！
Hi!
他就是我暴L雨中的港
Our... port in the storm!
e^^了！
Don't get overexcited!
是槲遮L跤甑姆孔
our gingerbread house!
就一次...我磉@...o你好|西
For once... Here I come...Bearing Treats!
就是它了？
So is this it?
不是我自F，我花了一小r砼渌
An honour student didn't show, so I had an idle hour to fill.
你做@用了一小r
You made that in an hour?
帕{丁（一N痛）加岱龋花了我一小r十分R
Well... Panadine to morphine,in about an hour and 10!
如果你有嵯⑼
If you get rid of the paracetamol...
你知道怎N做
...do a few things...
15分R之冗B同岱纫黄鸺舆M海洛因
...and morphine to heroin in 15 minutes.
xx，伙
Thankyou, you guys!
重新排列
Rearrange the atoms...
取出一c
...take a bit off...
放M一c
...put a bit on...
二乙酰岱
Liquid Diamorphine...
一般被Q楹Ｂ逡颍I制e的，高度
Commonly known as heroin,pharmaceutical grade, pure.
我Q之椤函狂耶d』
I call it "My Yellow Jesus!"
熊爸爸
Papa bear.
熊
Mama bear.
Baby bear.
P蒂f我必_始M一份力
It's just that... Candy says I have to start pulling my weight!
耶
Yeah.
你了解同性伴H
What do you know about gay escorts?
同性僭碓蕉
Growth market.
介意我一些技g上的}幔
Would you mind if asked you a few technical questions?
我]什N想跟你f的！
There's nothing I'd rather discuss with you!
他希望你做什N？
What do they expect you to do?
公@e有一大堆同性伲
Well there's a big down in the park!
你槭颤N不去研究研究！
Why don't you pop down and do some research!
我是f...
I mean...
如果他o你X，他希望你的o勃起幔
If they pay you, would they expect you to have a stiffie?
勃起的o有用的
It Helps!
我不J槲夷苣幼
I don't think I could manage that.
我只是洗洗手而已
I'm just washing my hands.
那好吧！
Alright!
他注N他的卡
He'll cancel his cards.
如果我先遇到他,事情就不像F在@恿.
Not if I get to him first.
_.._.._基！_芴萍{德
M. Ro. Roger. Rog. Rogie baby!Roger, Donald.
_芴萍{德，在@海
R.D. Here it is!
_芴萍{德莫伊m，彼得森^查斯街48
R.D. Moylan，48 Charles Street, Petersham.
他跟
He'll trace the call.
@就是l明A付的原因
That's why they invented prepaid phones.
啊，嗨，_埽
Ah, Hi! Roger?
是_苣伊m幔
Is that Roger Moylan?
看，看，@很y...
Yeah, Look! Look, This is hard...
是我偷了你的X包
I'm the guy who stole your wallet.
不，e欤∥艺fΣ黄穑行了吧？
我打就是榱说狼福我真的很抱歉！
Yep! No, hold on! I'm sorry, okay?
That's why I'm calling! I'm really sorry!
我只是...欠了一些，我想要一些F金...而且你啥也]有...
I just... I was after some money,
I saw some cash... and you had none...
我想您X包！
I want to give your wallet back!
是的，我知道，我很蠢！我只是，只是...
No, I know! I feel so stupid!It's just that I'm...
感到非常孤寂...
I'm so lonely right now...
我]有X，我碜园⒌氯R德(澳大利南部城市)
I've got no money,I've just come from Adelaide...
我]有朋友...
And I've got no friends...
我看X包在座位上，我就拿了，我想都]想！
You know, I saw the wallet on the seat,
and I took it! I wasn't thinking!
我δ愕男庞每]有任何d趣
And I'm not interested in your credit cards.
我只是想做Φ氖拢把X包o你
I just want to do the right thing and give it back to you.
啊...那好，不！F在不是r候，我...
Uhh...  Well, no! I mean now's not a good time, I...
我φ件事有c壕o
I'm a little bit nervous about this whole thing anyway!
我可以...明天早上再碰面
Can we just...Let's meet in the morning!
你c...c上班？
What...What time do you go to work?
你住在彼得森，幔
So you're in Petersham, right?
嗯...那下面有EA形的足球或者e的什N？
Umm... Isn't there a footie oval down there or something?
我用最斡行Х绞揭面吧
How about we meet out in front of the greyhound stand?
九c半可以幔
9:30? Is that good?
那好，我到r戴{色的棒球帽
Well I'll be wearing a blue baseball cap!
注意！著，@是我的a！
Look! look, Take my number!
你有P幔亢玫...
You got a pen? Yep, Right...
- 0422 844 881- [@是我家管道工的a！]
- 0422 844 881 - [That's my Plumber's!]
是的，881
Yes, 881.
好吧，你有移与吧，f一...
Well, have you got...a mobile just in case there's a...
是的...是的...嘿，告V我一件事...
Yeah... Yeah! Hey, Tell me one thing...
你是的C件照怎N@N可郏
How did you manage to get such a cute photo on your license?
很抱歉！非常抱歉，我扯太h了！
I'm Sorry! Yeah, I'm sorry, I go too far!
好吧，9c半，到r候
Alright! 9:30 then! I'll see you then!
很好，xx你，_埽再
Alright, Thanks Rog! Okay, bye!
丹，想象一下榱巳祟的福祉而\用你的力量
Imagine if you'd turned your powers
to the benefit of mankind... Dan!
@看起硐裎幔
Does this look like me?
一c阂膊
Not even remotely.
我可以借用一下你的眼R！
I could use these!
有c像...
And a bit of...
F在如何？
...How about now?
戴眼R的白N人
Caucasian man with glasses.
棒O了~
Yes!
我X得自己像人猿泰山
I felt like Tarzan,at fuckin' last!
我得去椤汉』（指P蒂）C取食物了
I had to hunt down some food for Jane.
我知道我大妄橐换亓
I knew it was in my power to do something brave.
是的...
Yeah...
你回k公室後，我可以幔
Can we talk about this when you get back to the office?
20分R之後...好的，再！
20 minutes... Okay, bye!
很抱歉！
Sorry about that!
早上好，你好幔
Good morning,How are you?
很好，你好幔
Ah, good!How are you?
好
Good.
我是想核σ幌吗N~
I just uh, wanted to check my
current balance on this please!
好的，一下你的人Re
Okay, I'll just need to get you to
enter in your PIN...
哦，天哪，我..感X糟透了
Oh God, I'm...terrible with this!
天哪！你有^不住人Re的困_幔
God! Do you ever have trouble remembering your PIN?
於不住底值娜四愦_感到@
You'd be surprised at the number of
people who forget them.
我知道，所以我M...
Yeah I know! That's why I came inside...
我在ATMC外面不住密a，我想...
Because I couldn't remember it
out at the ATM, and I thought...
如果我有身份C，我可以，呃...
You know I could just er..If I had ID?
不！很抱歉，你需要人Re斫灰
No! I'm sorry, you need your PIN number for all transactions. It's...
@是安全保障之一
It's one of those security things!
是的，然，然，我理解
No! Of course, of course!I understand. Um...
你不能通融一下..
So you can't just...
我真的不能！
I really can't!
喂？
Hello?
-莫伊m先生幔 -你是？
-Mr. Moylan? -Yes?
-_苣伊m先生幔 -怎N？
-Mr. Roger Moylan?  -Yes?
_苣伊m，我是邦y行安全部T的伊f道格拉斯
Roger Moylan, This is Ewan Douglasfrom
the Commonwealth Bank Security division...
是的，有事幔
Yes? Is something the matter?
在^去的24小r我留意到您信用卡的一些非正常的交易
We've been tracking some unusual activity on
your credit card, in the last 24 hours...
哦，不！
Oh no!
您最後一次使用主卡是在什Nr候？
When was the last time you used your Master Card?
著！我的X包昨晚被偷了...
Um, look! I think my wallet was stolen last night...
您笫Я幔
Did you report it missing?
我正在打笫В
I was just calling now!
但@是我o您打的
But I called you.
我是f我正要o你打
Um, I mean I was about to call.
莫伊m先生，我要核σ幌履的信息
Sir, Mr. Moylan, I'm going to have to
verify your details for a security check.
可以告V我您的出生日期幔
Would you please tell me your
Date of Birth?
嗯...1977年3月13
Um... 13th of March, 1977.
您母H的姓氏是？
Mother's Maiden Name?
呃，林奇
Er, Lynch.
您的安全a？
Number of security?
是人Re幔
Is that like your PIN number?
不一定...但一般都是！
Well, it shouldn't be...but you often find that it is!
嗯...3279
Umm...Try... 3279
某些日子，你忘所有的事情
It's just one of those days, you know...
where everythings just gone!
常有的事！
It happens all the time!
嗯，著...我已取到每日限~
Um, but listen... I've already got my daily limit out from the ATM outside...
但是我需要更多，我想I下一v老式的梅德斯
...But I actually need more, because
I'm trying to buy this beautiful old Mercedes....
奶油色的，你知道的，TLS？
...you know, the cream ones,you know, the TLS?
f回恚那些人是要收F金
Anyway, the guy's willing to negotiate for cash...
2247K
...$2247.
天哪，我成F光蛋了
God, we're going to be in the poor house!
50分！
...and 50 cents.
千feσ惠v痈星椋
Never get sentimental about a car!
我本硪你查一下@卡的可用~度...
I might just get you to check the
available credit on this card...
我可以取F幔
I can get a cash advance, can't I?
P蒂？P蒂！
Candy? Candy!
我做到了，我他做到了，！
I did it! I did it! I fucking did it, baby!
我他真的做到了！
I fucking did it!
天，你榇鬯牢业模
God, You... are going to fucking LOVE me for this...
7千K！
7 Grand!!
天！你看看它！我太ゴ罅耍它就像...
Oh god! You should have seen it!
I was fucking great! It was like...
就像那部影
It was like that movie we saw with that...
天，他叫啥碇，那我喜g的演T？
God, what was his name,that actor we like?
他得到了所有的X，他直酷懒 -丹尼！
...and he gets all that money,and he walks in and he's all coool,
and stuf like that... -Danny!
我言辛
I'm pregnant.
糟糕
Shit.
P蒂
Candy.
垃圾
Crap.
@不可能..呃..
It couldn't be, uh...
不
No.
我]弄破安全套啊！
We never broke a condom.
我早就知道
I'd know.
是我弄你^的那晚
It was the night I broke your skull.
太狂了
How fucking weird.
一晚就焉狭
One night.
我可以去做人流
I can get an abortion.
不行
No.
不，不行！
No, no way!
可以的
This is good.
@是注定的
It was meant to be.
@正是我需要的
This is what we need.
我必戒毒了
We've got to stop using.
是的
Yeah.
是的，然
Yeah, of course.
要糖幔
Sugar?
缮
Two, please.
我要告V所有人
We've got some news everybody...
我有孩子了
We're having a baby.
啊，H鄣
Ah, Darling!
P蒂甜心，太棒了
Candice, Good God.
我必明_一些事情
We just wanted you to know that
we've made some decisions. and uh...
我A留一部分X出眇B孩子
We've been putting some money aside,haven't we?
我要x_@"}"
We're going to get out of that
whole warehouse environment.
住M更m合居住的房子
...and live in a proper house.
是的，我要在一真正的『家』中
Yeah! We really want to raise our child in the....
...⒑⒆羽B大
...in a proper home.
你告V你的父母了幔
Have you told your parents?
]有
No.
第一天
Day 1
我知道我要做什N
We knew what we had to do.
有很多R\
It takes alot of planning to stop.
上天保佑！我一定可以做到，P蒂！
Lucky at last!We can really do this, Candy.
m然很Dy，但是...
It's going to be hard, but...
就像一座
I'm sure it's like a bridge...
只要我走^它，一切都好起
And once we cross it,everything will be okay.
你可以^m了...
You can get back into your painting again...
也S我搬到l下去...
Maybe we'll move to the country...
N一c蔬菜...
Grow some veggies...
B字浑u...
Feed the chickens...
我搬到泰...
We could go live in Thailand...
泰很好，只要我不吸毒的
Thailand would be great,if we didn't use.
或者去喜R拉雅山
Or the Himalayas.
我⒆上木舟
We'll go canoeing...
在白色的浪花上漂流
A bit of white water rafting...
eO健康，甜美入睡
Get healthy, sleep well...
不用再受毒品的控制
...not have drugs in our system.
那釉有多好？
How good would that be?
我必戒毒
We really have to do this.
我@次一定要做到
We have to do it this time.
是的，我的
Yeah, we will.
我
We are.
我正在努力
We're really fuckin' doing it!
第二天
Day 2
第四天
Day 4
我受不了了
I can't do it.
我忍不住了
嘿！回床上恚
Hey!Come back to bed.
你著龅
Alright? You'll catch a cold.
卡斯珀，是我，P蒂
Casper, It's Candy.
你拿到R上o我
Ring me as soon as you get this.
我打^你手C
We've tried your mobile.
我知道我f^一旦我要你就不理我但是...
I know we said to ignore us while we did this, but...
三天了...
3 days...
...我已很出色了，但是我F在感X不是很好
...we did pretty well, but we're not feeling so great now.
我F在很需要你
We don't want you to ignore us now.
你在幔
Are you there?
在就f
Pick up if you're there.
f呀！
Pick up!
好吧，你不在
Okay, you're not there.
o我
Call us!!
的！的！
Shit! Shit!
Shit! Shit! Shit!
科芸幔课沂P蒂啊！
Kojak? It's Candy!
嗯...的，很不好
Um... Shit, not so good.
我很痛苦，我的意思是
I'm really sick. I mean...
我需要信u
We just need credit.
呃...我去工作，之後我X的
Uh... I can work a shift,and then I can pay you back.
是的，我可以B那些一起了
Yeah, well if I work a shift,then I can pay that too.
我y受成@痈本不能工作
I can't work when I'm this sick!
好的，再
Ok, bye.
狗日的！
Fucking cunt!!
P蒂
Candy.
-P蒂  -哦，天哪
-Candy. -Oh God!
接
Answer!Answer, please!
他正要接
He was just about to answer!
-o我  -我要用！
-Give me the phone.-I want the fucking phone!
e拿我的，不行，不可以！
Don't fucking take it away from me!No! No!!
-我可以做到的   -不，L_！不！！！
-We can do it. -No! Get away!! Nooooo!!
P蒂，你在流血
Candy, you're bleeding.
你怎N流血？
Why are you bleeding?
羊水破了，她的miU了
The water has broken.Her cervix has dilated.
@是我不意看到的
This is what we didn't want to happen.
我都知道@是o法避免的流a
We call this an inevitable miscarriage.
我M力了
There's no going back.
我努力向P蒂解的r候，她正不得不受...分娩的痛苦
As I was explaining to Candy,she's going to
have to go through a kind of... labour!
我不知道那持m了多久，你必言羞^u知道那^程
I don't know however long that takes, you need to know that at this state of the pregnancy...
孩子]能蚧钕
...the baby is not going to survive.
真Σ黄
I'm Sorry.
o我哌替啶（一N人工合成的痛和催眠）
Give me pethidine!
我需要哌替啶！
I want pethidine!
你不想o她哌替啶幔
Will you give her the fucking pethidine, or what?
她在是太痛苦了，y道你]看？
She's fucking in pain,can't you see this?
就@樱P蒂，用力！
That's it! Candy, push!
快出砹耍用力，α耍。
Almost there! Push! That's it!!
我可以抱抱幔
Can I hold it?
t生，他的腿恿
Doctor, its leg moved.
只是d而已
It's just a spasm.
他明明恿耍
It moved!
就是d！
It's just a spasm.
地z
Hell
-你了多少X？ -50
-How much did you get?  -50.
那家伙又砹
That guy is still back there.
-也S你u一c，幔 -好吧
-Maybe you'll sell some. Yeah? -Alright.
我所做的一切
Everything we ever did...
都阎美好的望
we did with the best of intentions...
但是..年鸵荒辏事c`！
But.. events tumble!and the years pile up.
σa君子碚f，世界是渌访噪x的
The world is very bewildering to a junkie.
耶，我都很棒
Yeah, we're all good!
-度不  -靠！
-Well... Tastes bad. -Fuck!
_始吧
Here you go.
你察X到什N了幔
Do you feel anything?
]啊
No.
-的！ -我靠！
-Shit!  -Shit!
你仍然猿炙枷氲霓D
and still... you cling to the concept of change.
嘿，舒曼
Hey, Schumann...
我正打算搬到l下住一
...we are thinking of moving up the country for a while.
美沙酮(一N痛)
Give methadone a try.
@|西有什N不同？
What the fuck difference would it make?
可以空馇逍
The air's cleaner, for one.
@是N房
It's a kitchen.
有c暗，不是幔
It's a bit dark, isn't it?
是的
Yeah.
是的，我可以..
Yeah, we Could um...
打一洞.._天窗
knock out a hole...and put a skylight.
我勰
I love you.
有冷銮喽幔
Any frozen peas?
]
No.
我找到一，在那
I got one! There he is!
一直是u霜
It was all the way down in the turbo frost.
你早上竟然]有准
I can not believe you didn't do this, this morning.
他啥r候到？
What time are they coming?
日了！！
Fuck!!
生a日期是多少？
What's the date?
哦，不，^期一月了
Oh no, this expired a month ago.
你自己看，y死了！
Look at that! It smells bad!
-整N房都臭了！-y道不是幔
-That's got that kind of chicken smell!
-Yeah it does，doesn't it!
e心，H鄣模我有很多|西可以用碚{味
Not to worry, we'll just baste it in lots of stuff!
Like uh...
比如薄荷~、月桂~什N的？
Basil, uh... honey?Bayleaves or something?
e有什N？
What's in the cupboard?
你用什N烤肉呢？
What do you put on a roast?
你到@夯了多Lrg？
How long did it take you to get out here?
大概1小r40分R？H鄣模
Oh, About an hour and 40 minutes? Dear?
是的，大s40，是45分R？
Yeah, about... 40? 45?
不堵?
Much traffic?
不，一路惩
No, pretty good run really.
o可挑剔
Can't complain.
@禾美了，_是N享受
It's so beautiful here,
the drive down was so beautiful.
是啊，@是l村
Yeah, it's... Countryside.
找工作有著落了幔
Had any news on the job front?
~..行吧..@旱位不是很多，我靠救金^得去
Um... Well it's pretty... There's not much work around here.
We're getting by on the dole.
那N，看砦乙找份工作Na家用了
Well, apparently I might be able to
get some work hay bailing.
Na家用？
Hay bailing?
-哦！辛苦工作，勉糊口？-是的
-Ooooh! Tough work, hay bailing!-Yeah.
既然@樱我兔ψ鲲吧
So! What can I do in the kitchen?
不需要，真的，我能行！
Nothing mum, really! It's fine!
U，一定有什N我能兔Φ
Nonsense, there must be something I can do to help.
我自己就能搞定
Everything's under control.
t子_了
The oven's heating up.
我有些落伍了
We're running a bit behind.
e心，伙
No worries, mate.
@真是y以置信，你煞M苦心就是榱苏我到@
Oh This is unbelievable.You go to all this trouble
to invite us up here...
而且你竟然不能按r准湟徊捅泔
...and you can't even manage the simple decency of getting the meal together on time!
e管我，
Get off my case, mum!
食物在其次
Is not food that's even the issue here.
}是你的B度
It's your attitude!
好吧，我都冷o，午不到一小r就好了
Okay, let's just calm down. Lunch will be ready
in less than an hour.
l想睃c壕疲
Who wants some wine?
那u肉像石^！
That chicken is rock solid!
我午夜前不打算吃|西
We're not going to be eating before midnight.
蔬菜在哪耗兀
And where are the vegetables?
嘿，嘿，大家都o一o，H鄣
Hey hey, Let's all calm down, honey.
你在想什N？
What do you think is about?
周日午餐，本砗芎蔚囊患事
Sunday Lunch.It's a pretty simple thing.
但是你z一胶停就]蔚氖
But with you two, there's no such thing as simple.
毒品！
The drugs!
你就知道吸毒！
The drugs always come first.
不，不是那拥
Hey no, that is not true.
我F在已做的很好了
We're doing really well now.
你知道什N
Do you have any idea...
你ξ业募彝ザ甲鲞^什N？
...what you have done to my family?
ξ夷兀
To me?
那美的女孩怎N啦？
What happened to that beautiful girl?
怎N了？
What happened?
y道你看不？
Can't you see?
y道你不明白？
Don't you understand?
我六q起就攥o了拳^
I have been clutching my fucking fists
since I was 6 years old.
看看我的拳^，仔看看
Look at my fucking fists!
Look at them!
看看他，你@
Look at them, you fucking bitch!
y道你不明白
Don't you understand?
我明白！我握o我的手！
No! I gotta clench my hands!
我握o我的手不放松
I gotta clench my hands! I can't relax.
H鄣模H鄣模快看！@是大幼鳎
Darling, darling! Look!It's been a big move.
@是不平凡的一年
It's been a big year.
有很多化
There's been lots of changes.
你失去了一孩子
C'mon, you've lost a child.
但是你的生命B在一起，我可以看到
But you ARE getting your lives together.I can see that!
去吧
Just go.
L！
Fuck off.
忘午餐的事吧
Forget lunch.
可以幔
Can we?
可以取消午餐幔
Can we cancel the lunch?
我可以另外挑好日子
Maybe we can just make this another day.
今天不行，我很抱歉
Today is just a bad day.I'm sorry.
我好怕
I'm scared.
]什N可怕的
There's nothing to be scared of.
你X得我Y束了幔
D'you think we're going to end?
-我永h不Y束  -的
-We'll never end. -It'll end.
@不管用
It's not gonna work.
是流感疫苗幔
Is that the flu vaccine?
是
It's medicine.
它指引我免於T惑
It's leading us not into temptation.
嘿，P蒂，看看@
Hey Candy, check out this.
招泥水工
Brickie's labourer.
-我要打  -打吧
-I'll give it a call, eh. -Why don't you do that.
-嗨 -嘿
-Hi.-Hey!
@是保_,他住在@l路的上方
This is Paul. He lives up the road.
你好！
Good day.
他有些家庭自制好|西
He's got some good home grow.
太好了，我能多弄一些幔
Great.Can I get some more?
嗯，已]有了
Um... There is none left.
那我要一杯啤酒
Then I'll grab a beer.
也]有了
There's none of that either.
我要出去爽一下
I'm gonna go and get some more pot.
呃..我不吃晚餐了幔
Uh.. We gonna grab some dinner,or What?
不，你吃！我不用
No, you eat! I'll be fine.
你需要X幔课医Y工Y了
You want some money? I got paid.
-不 - ]P系的，伙
-No. -No, it's okay mate.
你去哪毫耍
Where were you?
y道你不打算f拙潆y的幔
Don't you fuck this one with your negative comments.
你在乾嘛？
What are you doing?
回到我的g之中
Going back to my art.
y道@δ阌惺颤N意x幔
Does not mean anything to you?
你和那家伙上床了幔
Have you been fucking that guy?
你在胡f八道
You do not know what you're talking about.
你整晚上都去哪毫耍
Where have you been all night?
hx你
Away from you.
你跟他上床了，ΣΓ
You fucked him, didn't you?
首先...
Firstly...
你在胡f八道
...You do not know what you're talking about.
其次...
Secondly...
我你的音
...I hate the sound of your voice.
第三...
Thirdly...
你他o我L蛋
...Why don't you just fuck off?
我是J真的
I mean, really!
L你的蛋!
Fuck off!
醒醒，醒醒
Wakey wakey.Hands off snakey!
那死的|西是啥
What the fuck is that?
如你所，你J槭巧叮
A statement of fact.What do you think it is?
P你什N事？
And what's this with your mother anyway?
如果不是她
Well if it's not her...
那N你
...Then you.
很好
Great.
好吧..你
Okay...You.
你自作明，其是子！
You think you're so smart,but youre just fuckin' mad!
f得好，P蒂
That's really good, Candy.
f得好，很高d你@N想
That's good, glad you think that.
你是混蛋人！
Your a fuckin' poet!
曾，有一δ信名叫丹和P蒂
Once upon a time, there was a Candy and Dan...
那年一切都很火
Things were very hot that year...
所有的蜡T都在渖先诨
All the wax was melting on the trees...
他在_上蠕樱到攀爬，樗做任何事
He would crawl on balconies, climb everywhere. Do anything for her...
我的丹尼男孩
My Danny boy.
成千上f的B海最小的B貉bc著她的秀l
Thousands of birds. Thetiniest birds adorned her hair...
一切都是金色的
Everything was golden...
一天晚上，欲火c燃了C床
One night the bed caught fire...
他L度翩翩，牡们〉胶锰
He was handsome, and a very good criminal...
我住在光和巧克力m殿e
We lived on sunlight and chocolate bars...
午後v情狂g
It was the afternoon of extravagant delight...
丹尼，b而走U的鹗
Danny, the Daredevil...
P蒂槟闫矶\
Candy the blessing...
那天的N~般巡游
The day's last rays of sunshine cruise like sharks....
@次，我要你的k法
"I wanna try it your way this time!"
你如此迅速地M入我的生命，K且我喜g
You came into my life really fast, and I liked it.
我在g愉的泥糁心氲梅鬯
We squelched in the mud of our joy.
我p腿潮瘢屈服於你
I was wet thighed with the surrender...
f物之中有l
Then there was a gap in things...
整大地都A斜了
And the whole earth tilted...
@就是我追S的
This is the business.This is what we're after.
你在我w龋伴著夜晚降R
With you inside me...Comes the night...、
y再入睡
... never again sleep ...
水池中的怪物
... a monster in the pool ...
黑暗本|的一部分，w翔
... Part of the black nature, to board ...
u和奔跑的青豆
... chickens and runnerbeans ...
我所看到的地方
... everywhere I looked ...
有r我恨你
... sometimes I hate you ...
星期五
... Friday ...
那K非我所指
... I didn't mean that ...
暴L雨..年鸵荒..有r我恨你
storm ... years ...... sometimes I hate you ...
床的一盆花
... a box of flowers by the bed...
我一r失手
... I broke your head ...
打破了你的^
... from the back of the bed ...
孩子死於清晨
... the baby died in the morning ...
我o他起了名字
... I gave him a name ...
他的名字叫托R斯
... His name was Thomas ...
可z的小家伙
...Poor little guy...
他的心像魔法鼓般跳
... his heart poundslike a voodoo drum ...
我的名字叫丹尼，我是a君子，我今天很乾Q，但不L久
My name is Daniel, I'm an addict.I'm clean today, but not for much longer.
L
Get out.
我想我那幼
I suppose I should do just that.
我在卡斯珀家
I am in my house Casper.
答我你停下
Promise me you'll stop.
答我你在我之前停下
Promise me you'll stop before me.
我是吉姆特，可以找丹接幔
can I talk to Dan Cutter,Please? It's Jim Wyatt here.
吉姆，是我
Yeah Jim, it's me.
嗨！P蒂住院了
Hi! Candy's in the hospital.
什N？
What?
她有c精神衰弱
She's suffered a bit of a nervous breakdown.
Y局很有趣，是幔
It's funny where it all ends up ，isn't it?
P蒂
Candy.
你]事喊桑
You okay?
我真被你到了
I was so frightened.
Σ黄
Sorry.
我不知道都l生什N了
I didn't really understand what was happening.
P蒂？
Candy?
一切都死亡了
Everything's dead.
一切都成{色的了
Everything's turning blue.
@很y承受
It's hard through all this you know.
我不在乎你曾怎犹度
I don't care how wrong you've
been living about your years.
我只在乎我的女
I care about my daughter.
什N？
What?
不管你能做什N，不管她要什N
Whatever you're capable of...
whatever she needs...
走吧，我你回家
Come on, we'll take you home.
他走
Let him go.
就那
And that was it...
一切都SL消散
That was all that was scattered to the winds...
卡斯珀消失了
Casper was gone...
舒曼消失了
Schumann was lost...
P蒂]有好D
Candy was off getting better...
海岸...
The coast...
改^w善
Rehab...
而我...
And I...Was...
我只是...
I was just...
清洗者，丹
The washer, Dan.
世界冠的清洗者
World Championship washer.
有一天，你榘拇罄清洗
One day, you'll wash for Australia.
@世界充M了奇思妙想
The world was full of startling new concepts.
我o法思考，o法呼吸
I couldn't think.I couldn't breathe.
我在等她回
I was waiting for her to come back.
因樗是我的一切
Because she was everything.
她是我的一切
She was everything to me.
嘿，丹，有人找你
Hey Dan, you have a visitor.
有人找
Visit.
跟她f我不在
Just Tell her I'm not here.
你了幔
Are you crazy?
告V她我不在！
Tell her I knocked off.
你的朋友砹耍快出戆
Your friend is right here, just come.
-你好 -嘿！
-G'day. -Hey!
我以槟忝魈炖u
I thought it was tomorrow.
我等不急了
I couldn't wait.
好
Is that okay?
挺好的
Yeah! No, it's good!
你真漂亮
It's just!You look so beautiful.
l下的空怵B人
It's all that country air.
我一小r後收工
So I finish in an hour.
丹
Dan.
丹，嘿，嘿！
Dan. Hey!Hey!
丹尼，丹尼！嘿！
Danny, Danny! Hey!
]P系的，嘿！
It's Okay.Hey!
嘿，]P系的，我砹
Hey, It's Okay,I'm here now.
我]有可能了
There's no going back.
如果你得以解
If you're given a reprieve...
你楹尾蝗ハ胂
I think it is good to remember...
想想那孩子有多瘦小
...just how thin it is.
〗K